这番茄酱渍怎么能变得这么硬啊
How could ketchup get this hard?
只需要用手这么握住 对它说
You just hold it in your hand like this, and say
你是我用过最"大"的番茄酱
you are the biggest ketchup I've ever had.
各位 得到啦 得到啦
Hey, everybody. I got it, I got it.
别紧张 早发现早治疗嘛
Don't panic. At least you caught it in the early stage.
错 我是指我有
No, I got the papers
刊登彩票中奖号码的报纸啦
so we can see if our ticket win the lottery.
-头奖有一亿两千万呢 -不错啊
- 120 million dollars. - Fun.
中奖的钱 相当于我信托基金的八分之一呢
If we win, I will get an eighth of my trust fund back.
快点吧 彩票在谁那里
Come on. Now, who's got our ticket?
在我这 我放这里了
I've got the ticket. I put it here.
我这里也算是一块洞天"福地"嘛
I figured it's for everybody else gets lucky.
对了 如果赢了
By the way, if we win,
我要在游乐园旁买个公寓
I'm gonna buy a condo right next to Great Adventure
天天醉醺醺地去游乐园玩
and go there everyday drunk.
还要在车库里摆个炫富用的饮料冰箱
Also put a soda fridge in my garage for show.
厄尔 如果赢了 你打算拿你那笔钱干嘛呢
Earl, what are you gonna do with your share if we win?
我会立马逃离这个火坑
Well, I'll get out of this club chop as fast as I can,
然后让自己坐拥后宫佳丽三千
and set me up with some kind of Hugh Hefner situation.
谜底要揭晓了 大奖最后花落谁家呢
Here we go, for the big money.
我要是赢了 立马去订云端影片台
Woo. If I win, hello Netflix subscription.
中奖号码是 6 10 5 12 和9号
We need a 6, a 10, a 5, a 12 and a 9.
我们第一个数字是6
And the first number is 6!
第二个数字是47
And the second number is 47.
幸好姐没付给你们彩票钱 白痴们
Good thing I didn't pay my share of the tickets yet, suckers!
趁还记得
Before I forget,
我去加印了小蛋糕店的名片
I printed up more of our cupcake business cards
方便我们去威廉斯堡手工艺品展时分发
So we can hand them out at the Williamsburg crafts fair.
哇 "迫不及待"啊
Oh, can't wait
陪你去白送人小蛋糕
Me and you handing out free cupcakes
还得跟一票卖毛织物 iPad套
stuck between hipsters selling crochet iPad sleeves
调味料以及调味料瓶的废柴嬉皮士混一起
and salt peppers and salt pepper shakers.
那不是白送 那叫做打开市场
We are not just giving them away for free. It's marketing.
顾客吃了满意 以口相传就能无人不知
One person eats it and spreads it around their friends.
我们跟疱疹一样以口相传啊
So we are herpes.
你好啊 苏菲
Hello, Sophie.
你再"甜"美一点 我的糖尿病就要病发了
If you looked any sweeter, you would fire up my diabetes.
厄尔
Oh, Earl.
为我缺胳膊少腿的男人多了
You wouldn't be the first man to lose a limb over me.
苏菲 你的大驾光临真是始料未及啊
Sophie, I'm surprised to see you in here.
江湖谣传你跟奥列格分手了呢
Stutter buzz says you and Oleg are no longer together.
哎哟 这小妞是个小八卦天后呢
Wow, this little girl likes to gossip. Yes?
大人的事小孩别插嘴
Won't you scutter your little butt over there
尽你的本份乖乖拿菜单来就行了
and get me the menu the way you are supposed to?
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Hey, Max, Caroline.
过来卡座一谈
Come see me in my booth.
坐这么远是因为
Are we over here so Oleg
奥列格没办法从厨房窗口看到你吗
can't see you through the kitchen window?
这里是哪里呀 是餐馆
What is this? Diner or
还是过期的《时尚》八卦杂志啊
back issue of Cosmopolitan magazines?
我小时候也爱读《时尚》
I grew up reading Cosmo.
小孩不该看的内容全有呢
I mean, what a six-year-old doesn't need to know?
例如 男性不为人知的敏感带是哪呢
The hidden male erogenous zones.
是乳头 报告完毕
It's the nipples, the end.
我是来通知你们明天有打扫的活
I came to give you girls a cleaning job tomorrow.
我们明天没空 要去参加手工艺品展
We can't tomorrow. We are doing the crafts fair.
我们放着正经钱不赚
We are turning down a real paying job
去白痴展白送吗
to go to the crap fair?
没错
Yes,
我们得"齐心"放"心思"进"去"小蛋糕生意啊
it's important that we focus on the cupcake business.
齐心 才能放心思进去啊
And you can't spell "focus" without "us".
"去"你妈的"去"咩
Or FU.
你好吗 苏菲
Hello, Sophie.
你好 奥列格
Hello, Oleg.
念念不忘巫山云雨吗
So, do you miss the sex?
我们俩还是赶紧跑吧
Oh, you know what? We should go.
别走 我们还在谈事呢
No. We are having a conversation here.
而且那巫山云雨只如浮云
And besides, the sex was not that good.
少来 明明是狂风暴雨
Oh, it was that good.
就只如浮云一般好吗
It wasn't that good.
求你了 放我们走吧
Please, I beg you. Let us go.
你走吧 我听得津津有味呢
You can go. I'm kind of into it.
这简直是下流版的《唐顿庄园》
Like, it's like a dirty Downton Abbey.
你还站在那里干啥呢
So why are you still standing there
穿着那条咖啡色天鹅绒裤
giving me those sad, cow eyes
装楚楚可怜啊
in that brown velure.
因为哥穿这个最帅
Because it's a good look on me.
而且我还在等你承认 你来是因为
And because I'm waiting for you to admit that you came here
你念念不忘我们的床第之欢
because you miss the sex.
我怀念明斯克的夏天
I miss summers in Minsk.
也怀念在医院里抽烟
I miss smoking in hospitals.
但我绝不怀念跟你翻云覆雨
But I don't miss the sex.
不承认拉倒 你想吃点什么
Fine, then. What would you like to eat?
老规矩 来根香肠先
I'll have my usual sausage.
熟了 在"这儿" 请慢用
Ok, ding. It's ready.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's homemade cupcakes.
麦克斯美味自制小蛋糕
Max's delicious homemade cupcakes
我来快进吧 麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Let's move this along. Max's homemade cupcakes.
麦克斯
Max.
别这样 你好歹
Come on. Could you at least try
配合一下 好好推销嘛
and have a better attitude at the crafts fair?
在那个教堂妞把老娘的头发
I was doing fine until my hair got
弄上帮派羽毛前 我一直很配合啊
gang feather by that girl from that church of good vibes.
您好
Hi!
我是后边的荷兰网型蛋糕摊的
I'm from the Funnel Cake booth back there
你们这可悲的小桌子
and your little table is sadder than
比丧礼还让人悲痛
watching the notebook at a funeral.
喂 荷兰妞
Hey Dutch girl,
这么爱指手画脚 不去堵水坝可惜啊
why don't you go stick your finger in a dyke.
旁边的大码牛仔裤肯定有洞让你堵
I'm sure you can find one over near the plus sized denim.
麦克斯 放轻松 我们都是商人嘛
Max, please. We are all business woman here.
是啊 不过某些商人把桌巾戴头上呢
Yeah. Some of us wearing table cloth on their heads.
我们是刚起步的小生意
Just so you know they make shift tables
所以才用简陋的移动桌子
cause we are just starting out.
我们才开始营业八个月
We've only been in business eight months.
海蒂 我们营业多久了啊
Heidi, how long have we been funneling?
全天候24小时 三个月无休
Everyday 24-7 for the past three months.
我们都有个摊位了
And we already have a booth.
说得没错
Yeah we do.
网型蛋糕 真因你们俩而无趣
I have to say you girls really take the fun out of funnel.
错 我们是把乐趣融入其中
Actually we put the fun in the funnel.
瞧 充满乐趣的网型蛋糕啊
See? You can't start "funnel" without "fun".
乐你妈的"去"
Or fu.
我们落后人家了 她们才开业三个月呢
Three months and they've already had a booth. We're behind.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's homemade cupcakes.
给我拿着
Take this!
瞧 成功了
See? Success!
恐吓别人来参与不叫成功
Scaring people into participating isn't success.
而叫科学神教
It's Scientology.
打电话给苏菲 那活儿我们接了
Calling Sophie we're taking that job.
你迟到最好有个好理由
You'd better have a good reason you're late,
因为我花不少时间把病鸽子羽毛
because I managed to get here on time
从头发上弄下来 也一样没迟到
despite removing the disease pigeon feathers from my hair.
我有
I do.
今天我们不是打扫那间公寓嘛
So today when we were cleaning up that apartment
当我把手放在一个陌生人的马桶里时
and I had my hands in a total stranger's toilet,
我意识到我们真想成功
I realized if we're really gonna be successful,
就必须得打破思维
we've got to think outside the bull.
所以当我把手彻底洗干净后
So after I thoroughly washed my hands,
我知道那是永远洗不掉的 对吧
I know they never really come off though, right?
如跗骨之蛆玷污你的灵魂
Off your soul, I mean.
我打了个电话找人拉关系
I made a call to a connection I know
给咱俩接了个蛋糕单子
and got us a real cupcake job.
还是在曼哈顿哦
And it's in Manhattan.
是某个社会名流之子的一岁生日
It's the first birthday party for the son of a socialite.
60个奶油糖霜的小蛋糕 击个掌吧
60 cupcakes with buttercream frosting. Up top.
奶油
Buttercream?
我可不想我的合伙人
This is not the response
给我这种反应哦
I was expecting from my business partner.
我要是的"哟呵" 干得好
I was expecting wooo! Awesome job!
太棒了 伙计
Thumbs up, buddy.
为什么 你的合伙人又不是儿童节目主持
Why? Is your business partner on a show of Nicklodeon?
听着 我不做奶油蛋糕
Look, I don't do buttercream.
奶油是个贱人
Buttercream is a bitch.
如果不把它冷藏好
If it doesn't stay refrigerated,
它会比名人的婚姻塌得还快
it falls apart as fast as a two-celebrity marriage.
这活儿一定要接 这是为了更上层楼
We have to take this job, it's the next step for us,
最近这些日子
cause all we're doing these days
我们不是打扫公寓 就只是在餐馆干活
is cleaning apartment and working at the diner.
我还做别的呢 去帮琵琪看孩子
That's not all I'm doing. I also babysit for Peach.
琵琪不介意呢
Oh, Peach is fine with it.
为什么琵琪会不介意
Why would Peach be fine with it?
本来我是想在儿童台式的
Look I was gonna tell you this
击掌欢呼之后告诉你的
after the Nickelodeon high five
结果你不愿意跟我击个掌
but that didn't happen and I got thrown.
我拉的关系就是琵琪啊
Peach is the connection I used to get us the party.
你居然擅自打电话 去求琵琪给我们找活儿
You called Peach without asking me and begged her for a job?
我没有求她
I didn't beg.
我只是问她有没有认识会用咱们的人
I ask her if she knew anybody who could use us
她也十分乐意的把
and she was more than happy
我们推荐给她朋友康斯坦斯
to recommend us for her friend Constance.
别想 我不爽这么干
No way, I'm not comfortable with this.
有时候你就得干一些自己都不爽的事情
Sometimes you have to do things that make you uncomfortable.
这就是成长
It's the way you grow.
不 成长是去森林趴喝醉之后
No, it's the way you get a ride home
被人拖上车 用"鸟"送回家
from a keger in the woods.
麦克斯
Max.
麦克斯 抱歉 但我们不能变成
Max, I'm sorry, but we can't turn into those people
那些为了柴米油盐拼命工作
who work and work just to pay their bill,
却没有时间追求梦想的人
and don't have any time to pursue their dreams.
你是指全美国人吗
You mean Americans?
我明天就告诉琵琪我们不干
I'm telling Peach tomorrow we're not doing it.
现在去给我拿点牛奶
Now go get some milk.
没问题 因为在其位谋其政
No problem, cause that's what waitresses do
我们这一生就只有服务生的命了
and apparently that's all we'll ever be.
干嘛
What?
证明跟他的翻云覆雨很普通嘛
I have to prove the sex was not that good.
奥列格 居然在食物上做
Oleg, on the food?
干嘛用这么嫌弃的语气
Don't say it like that,
我们进去之前 那火腿就淋过汁了
That ham was already glaced before we go there.
那你们俩算是复合咯
So I am guessing you are back together?
才没有呢 都说了只如浮云
Oh no no, the sex was not that good.
她都爽得飘飘欲仙了
Oh, it was that good.
我进去拿蛋黄酱
I went to get Mayo,
一切就迅雷不及掩耳地发生了
and it all happened so fast.
宝贝儿 来点时尚感
Ok babies, give me fashion,
来点表情 很好
give me a face, yeah.
琵琪 我不知道你在公寓里搞啥
Peach, I don't know what's going on in your apartment,
但我要先声明
but I would like it on the record:
我是非自愿的帮凶
I'm not a willing accomplice.
你到底在干嘛呢
So what is going on here?
布莱德如同本人 魅力十足
Well, Brad is giving us seduction like his name sake
而安吉丽娜亦是 木头一个
and Angelina is giving us nothing like her name sake.
这个布景看着真高级
This is pretty fancy set up,
那俩孩子被奥斯卡提名了吗
were the kids nominated for an Oscar?
最佳窘境表演奖之窘境双娃
Best performance by twins in a ridiculous situation?
这是我新妈咪博客的宣传照
It's a photo spread for my new mummy blog,
我称其为"妈咪与我" 很有想法吧
I'm calling it Mummy and Me. Isn't that clever?
还很"原创"呢
And original.
我朋友康斯坦斯开博客后 我也跟上了
I had a blog since my friend Constance started her blog,
我们俩都有博客 都有孩子
we both have blogs and we both have babies.
不同的是 她的孩子是从非洲领养的
Only her babies are adopted from Africa.
为了不输给她 我找了
She will be winning if I didn't have two
乡下穷苦白人家的人当代理孕母
from a poor white hellbilly surrogate.
关于你朋友康斯坦斯
About your friend Constance,
我好像得帮她办派对...
I think I was supposed to do a party for her.
麦克斯 千万别搞砸
Max, please don't screw this up
因为我恨她 同时又需要她爱我
because I hate her and I need her to love me.
我想说的是
Yeah, here is the thing.
感谢你的帮忙 但卡洛琳不该擅自打给你
Thank you, but Caroline should never have called you
让你帮我们忙
and asked you for a favor.
麻烦到你真是抱歉了
I'm not comfortable asking you to do that.
但我为了你伸出援手
But I did it, for you.
所以你也得为我伸出援手
And now you will do that for me.
麦克斯 这事务必得"一帆风顺"
And Max, this has to go swimmingly
这可是我刚学的新词哦
which is a new word I just learned.
你是说 我不能不干吗
So you are saying I can't get out of it?
我是说 麦克斯 你不能不干
I'm saying, Max, you can't get out of it.
麦克斯 还在因为琵琪的事不跟我说话吗
Max, still not talking to me because of the Peach thing?
好吧
Fine.
里面的奶油小蛋糕可真她娘的靓啊
Those are some pretty badass buttercream cupcakes,
都给爷在盒子里乖乖趴着等
ain't no drama going on in that box!
我都学黑帮腔调逗你了 也不赏脸笑一个吗
Ok, I just went gangster, and not even a smile?
干嘛啊 打算这辈子都不跟我说话了吗
What? Are you planning to never talk to me again?
你点头了 如果你是聋子 就算说话了
You nodded, if you were deaf that would be talking.
没错 我弟弟是聋子
That's true, my brother is deaf,
不是先天的 是玩烟火闹的
not from birth, from firecrackers.
别紧张 我们还有时间
Relax, we still have time.
再坐10分钟地铁 然后步行15分钟
Ten more minutes on the train and a 15-minute walk.
奶油不会这么快化的
The buttercreams are not gonna melt.
有人就喜欢用肢体语言制造恐慌
Some people just like to create non-verbal drama.
乘客们请注意
Attention passengers.
-前方铁路出现障碍物 -不是吧
- There is an obstruction up on the track ahead. - No.
我猜肯定是有人跳轨自杀
I bet someone jumped in front of the train.
天啊 悲剧啊
Oh my God, what a tragedy,
奶油该化了
the buttercream!
乘客们请注意
Attention passengers.
我们为延误深表歉意
We apologize for this delay.
前方铁路障碍物尚未排除
There is still an obstruction on the tracks ahead.
这障碍物绝对是尸体
It's totally like a body.
他们弄不掉还啥的
They can't get it off and what not.
列车很快就能开动
We should be moving shortly.
这家伙搞什么啊 这番话20分钟前都说过了
What is with this guy? He said that 20 minutes ago.
你的小蛋糕怎么样了 我的有点化了
How are your cupcakes? Mine are getting a little loose.
还这样 还不愿意说话是吗
Still? Still not talking?
好吧 麦克斯 那我也不说了
Fine, Max. Now I'm not talking neither.
她搞什么啊 这番话她20分钟前也说过了
What is with her? She said that 20 minutes ago, too.
她那嘴就是闲不下来啊
And she just keeps talking.
我知道
I know, right?
我们肯定是撞到人了
We probably hit the body.
血肉飞溅到轮子还啥的
So it is all up in the wheeling and what not.
如果我们轮子下真有啥的
Well, if there is what not under our wheels,
我就不能把小蛋糕送到目的地
and I don't get these cupcakes there,
我保姆的工作将不保
I'm going to lose my babysitting job.
-我们是保姆还是蛋糕师啊 -我在跟他说话
- Are we babysitters or bakers? - I was talking to him.
别多管闲事
Stay out of this.
姑娘[西语]
Nina,
如果你们俩是蛋糕师
if you two are bakers,
或许你们该把小蛋糕拿出来分一分
maybe you should break up some of those cupcakes,
好让我们不被饿死
so we all don't starve.
谁也别想碰这些蛋糕
No one is touching these cupcakes.
我们的未来全靠它们了
Our entire future is riding on these mothers.
我好像闻到了尸体的味道
I think I'm smelling like a, like a dead body smell.
小姐 你一直在让大家更恐慌
Miss, you are making things so much worse in here.
别告诉我你没闻到
Are you telling me you don't smell that?
闻起来就像我妹妹烧到自己时
It's like when my sister burned herself
把烟火扔向我弟弟耳朵那样
throwing firecrackers at my brother's ear.
列车停止运行
This train is out of service.
离下一站大约还有两个街区远
We are approximately two blocks away from the next station.
我们会带大家步行过去
We're gonna have to take you on foot.
请站成一排 我们会安全护送你们出去
Please form a single line and we will escort you to safety.
我们要走过去
We are gonna walk?
他们居然想让我穿着高跟鞋走地铁隧道
They expect me to walk through a subway tunnel in heels?
各位 被困住时 要先吃谁有人选了
Hey everybody, I think we know who we are gonna eat first.
天啊 这里热死了 得有90多度吧
My god, it's so hot up in here. It's like 200 degrees.
如果我不慎晕倒跌下去
If I faint and fall down,
老鼠们会生吃掉我还啥的
the others rats will like eat me and what not.
老鼠 麦克斯 这里还有老鼠啊
Rats? Max, are there rats?
地铁地板就是用老鼠铺出来的
It's a subway. The floor is made of rats,
不过你真该担心的是忍者神龟吧
but you really have to worry about, the ninja turtles.
谢谢你理我
Thank you for responding.
等等
Hold up.
我现在就告诉你
I'm telling you right now.
如果我因为这件事丢了我的保姆工作
If I lose my babysitting job over this,
你会比被老鼠吃掉更惨
the rats would be the better option for you.
我们离下一站就两个街区 肯定能赶到
We are only two blocks from the station. We can still make it.
你的小蛋糕怎么样了
How are your cupcakes?
它们还没有散
They are still holding together.
就像咱们 我们还没有散
Like us. We are still holding together.
拜托 别在这惺惺相惜了 少说话多走路吧
Geez, come on, don't bring gal. Less talk more walk.
伙计们 这里有个缺口
Folks, It's a bit of gap here.
缺口 不可能 怎么会有缺口呢
A gap? There can't be a gap. Why is there a gap?
因为人们需要合理价位的基本衣着啊
Because people need reasonably price basics.
我先跳过去 然后在那边接你们
I'm gonna hop across and help the rest of you over.
小姐 到你了
Hey miss, you are next.
我一边用手电照着 你抓着我吧
I put the light on, just grab it.
我在隧道里听人让我"抓"他无数次了
You know how many times I heard that from a guy in the tunnel?
帮我拿着这个
Hey, just take these.
先生 小心点 那可是奶油
Careful, sir, it's buttercream!
我把包包扔给你 接好啦
I'm throwing you my purse. Here it comes.
谢谢 谢谢各位
Thank you. Right. Thank you.
好了 小姐 到你了
Ok, miss, you next.
把蛋糕递给我 然后跳过来
Hand me over the cupcakes and jump.
我不敢 我好害怕
I can't. I'm terrified.
我跌倒了怎么办 老鼠会咬我的
What if I fall? The rats will eat me.
这种伤痛我一辈子都无法忘记
I can never come back from that.
破产 没事 老鼠 大事
Bankruptcy? Yes. Rats? No.
"卡洛琳 你的脚趾呢
"Hey Caroline, where are your toes?"
这说来话长了..."
"Well, it's a long story."
姑娘 如果你跌到供电轨道上
Girl, if you fall that third rail,
你在被老鼠咬之前 就会被电熟了
it will fry you way before the rats get there.
听着 玛利亚 你要吓死我啊
Listen, Mariah, you are freaking me out.
我们走运的话 老鼠会咬掉你的嘴
If we're lucky, the rats will eat your mouth.
卡洛琳 没事的 就跨出这一步吧
Caroline, it's ok. It's just a step. Take the step.
帮我拿着
Hold these.
快点 我在这等你
Come on, I'm right here.
我跨出了一步 现在该轮到你了
I took the step, now you have to take the step.
说得对 你做了 我也要做
That's right. You did. I do.
那开始吧
Here we go.
各位后退 快点
Back up everybody. Yeah!
卡洛琳加油 卡洛琳加油
Go Caroline, go Caroline, go.
Go Caroline, go Caroline.
我看见老鼠了 我们四目相对了
I saw a rat. We made eye contact.
或许你把高跟鞋脱掉
You know what? It would probably be easier
会比较容易跳
if took those heels off.
先生 打死我都不可能
Sir, that is never going to happen.
这里可是曼哈顿
We are in Manhattan.
虽然是在地下 但我仍身在其中
I may be under it but I'm still in it.
当别人救出我被吃掉一半的尸体时
And when they pull out my half-eaten body,
穿着高跟鞋才算死得体面
I will be wearing my heels.
玛丽亚
Mariah?
干嘛 我就吃了一个而已
Why? I only have one.
你能怎么样
What are you gonna do?
跳回来打我还啥的吗
Jump back over and do something and whatnot?
康斯坦斯 抱歉我们迟到了
Constance, we're sorry, we are late.
我讨厌等 我从不等任何事物
I don't wait. I don't wait for anything.
我都已经有第八代iphone了
I already have the iPhone 8.
抱歉 我们也没办法
Sorry, we couldn't help it.
我们刚被困在地铁里了
We were trapped on the subway.
快把小蛋糕放在盘子里
Well, just put some cupcakes on a plate
因为门外有一屋子女人
cause I got a roomful of women out there
等着拿刀把东西切一半
who need to cut something in half
然后吃掉另一半
and then eat the other half,
她们等不及了
and they need to do it now!
欢迎回到曼哈顿 蛋糕卖相如何
Welcome back to Manhattan. How do they look?
它们看起来像刚在里面不戴套杂交了一番
Like they all had unprotected sex with each other?
你们俩好呀 我是来找宝宝的
Oh, how are you two? I'm looking for the babies,
我找了10秒钟 打算放弃了
I'm about just ten seconds I'm just giving up.
-琵琪 小蛋糕出了点问题 -最好别
- Peach, there is a problem with the cupcakes. - There can't be.
康斯坦斯会杀了我的 真的宰掉我
Constance will kill me, literally.
她的前两个闺蜜都失踪了
Her last two best friends went missing.
这卖相也太差了吧
That is not attractive at all.
难道所有食物是长这样的吗
Is... is that what food looks like?
为什么小蛋糕还不端出来
Why are there no cupcakes out?
如果你俩是我的佣人 我早驱逐你们出境了
If you two work for me, I deport you.
小蛋糕出了点状况
There is a bit of cupcake situation.
在赶来的路上 奶油有点融化了
The buttercream sort of broke down on the way up.
这不是什么大问题 还能补救
It's not a problem, we can fix it.
我去便利店买材料上来润色一下
I'll just run to a delly get what we need to touch them up
没人会察觉的
and no one's the wiser.
我要负全责
And I take the full responsibility.
我的合伙人曾警告过我 奶油是贱人
My partner warned me that buttercream was a bitch.
我不是对你无礼 这是烘培术语
I'm not being rude, that's technical baking term.
就这卖相 你还指望我掏300块啊
You expect me to pay 300 dollars for these?
卡洛琳·钱宁 不得不说
Caroline Channing, I have to say
你比你老爸还坑人
that you're a bigger con artist than your father.
那我也不得不说 你比奶油还贱
Then I have to say you're a bigger bitch than the buttercream.
我不是你老板 不能打你
I'm not your boss, so I can't hit you.
不过我相信琵琪也不会是你老板了
But I'm sure that Peach won't be your boss much longer either.
对吗 琵琪
Right, Peach?
可我爱麦克斯
But I love Max.
自打我买了双胞胎后 她就一直帮我照料
She's been with me since I bought the twins.
没了她我活不下去
I can't live without her.
那以后你别想参加我的任何派对
You are never coming to another one of my parties.
麦克斯 你被解雇了
Max, you're fired.
是我不好让你丢了工作 我内疚死了
It's my fault. You lost your babysitting job, and I feel awful.
是我骂那个贱人"贱"的
Hey, I'm the one who call that bitch a "bitch".
等我们被驱逐出境时
And I'm gonna write those awesome films
我要把这些精彩的瞬间铭记下来
right up until we got evicted.
何不承认跟我翻云覆雨的爽翻天了呢
Why can't you just admit that the sex was that good?
你知 我知
You know it, I know it,
冷藏库里有牙印的火腿也知啊
the ham with the bite marks in the freezer knows it.
好吧 的确是爽翻天
Ok, fine. The sex was that good,
火腿也好吃到爆
as was the ham.
会爽到爆是因为这不单纯是性
It was that good because it was more than just sex.
还有爱
It was love.
不 那不是爱
Oh... it is not love.
不 那就是爱
Oh, it is love.
不 那不是爱
Oh... it is not love.
那只是下流龌龊的性而已
It was dirty, disgusting sex.
说得没错
Yes, it was.
奥列格 你是真的爱苏菲吗
Oleg, do you really love Sophie?
是的 总有一天我会吻上她的唇
Yes, I do. And one day I will kiss her.
她的朱唇终将属于我
Her lips will be mine.
你从来没吻过她吗
Wait, you never kissed her?
吻的不是脸上的双唇
Not on the lips of her face.
不过那天迟早会来的
But that day will come.
天啊 真不敢相信我会说这种话
Man, I can't believe that I'm actually saying this,
但他那番话真是浪漫到爆
but that is pretty freaking romantic.
我找麦克斯 她的姓好像是"布莱克[黑人]"
I'm looking for Max, I think her last name is "Black".
无意冒犯 也可能是叫"非裔美籍"
Oh, sorry, maybe it's "African American"?
你说她的名字是"麦克斯·非裔美籍"吗
You think her name is "Max African American"?
琵琪 你来这儿干嘛 双胞胎谁看着呢
Peach, what're you doing here? Who's with the twins?
他们在车里 别担心
They're in the car, don't worry,
我把门窗全都关死了 他们很安全的
I rolled up the windows and locked the doors, so they're safe.
麦克斯 抱歉在康斯坦斯面前
Max, I'm sorry for pretending
假装开除你
to fire you in front of the Constance.
假装的吗 感觉挺真的呢
Pretended? That felt pretty real.
我演技高超嘛
Yeah, I'm good.
我假装高潮时连自己都差点信以为真
My fake orgasms are so real even I believe them.
琵琪 这事全怪我 拜托别解雇麦克斯
Peach, this is all my fault. Please give Max her job back.
这就是我来这里的原因 麦克斯 回来吧
That's why I'm here. Max, come back,
我要你明天帮我看着双胞胎
I need you to watch them tomorrow,
以后的每一天也要
and then everyday.
琵琪 明天我恐怕没空
Peach, I don't think I can work for you tomorrow,
以后也不会有空了
or any other day.
我们得把重心放在我们生意上
We have to focus on our business.
麦克斯 你确定这样做你不介意吗
Max, are you sure you're comfortable with this?
当然不爽了 但这就是重点所在 不是吗
No, I'm not comfortable, but that's the point, right?
人必须迈出一步
You gotta take a step.
那再看一年如何
Well, then how about just for another year?
一年后 双胞胎就能自己照顾自己了
By then the twins will be old enough to take care of themselves.
不行 不过我保证有时间
No, but I promise I'll come by
我会去看望他们
and say "hi" to the twins whenever I can.
麦克斯
Oh, Max,
跟你一样又好又会说英语的保姆 世间难寻
I will never find someone as wonderful as you who speaks English.
再见 麦克斯
Bye, Max.
这对你我来说 都是件好事
Wow, good for you, good for us.
希望吧 这是第一份
Hope so. That's the first job
我没找到下家就辞去的工作
I ever quit without a job to take its place.
你有下家啊 为自己而工作
You have another job. You work for yourself.
当自己的老板
You're your own boss.
自己的老板
My own boss?
那我等不及要求升职而潜规则自己了
I can't wait to sleep with myself to get a promotion.